[
  {
    "question": "Hello darkness my old friend",
    "correct": "I've come to talk with you again",
    "song": "Hello darkness my old friend - Simon and Garfunkel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Shawty's like a melody in my head",
    "correct": "That I can't keep out got me singing like",
    "song": "Replay - Lyaz"
  },
  {
    "question": "Somebody once told me the world is gonna roll me",
    "correct": "I ain't the sharpest tool in the shed",
    "song": "All star - Smash Mouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Makin' my way downtown",
    "correct": "Walking fast faces pass and i'm homebound",
    "song": "A Thousand Miles - Vanessa Carlton"
  },
  {
    "question": "We're no strangers to love",
    "correct": "You know the rules and so do I",
    "song": "Never gonna give you up - Rick Astley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Give me reasons we should be complete",
    "correct": "You should be with him i can't compete",
    "song": "Slow dancing in the dark - Joji"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got the mojo deals",
    "correct": "We've been tripping like the 80s",
    "song": "The box - Roddy Rich"
  },
  {
    "question": "All i wanna say is that...",
    "correct": "They don't really care about us",
    "song": "They don't care about us - Michael Jackson"
  },
  {
    "question": "Heads up, you hear a sound, turn around and look up",
    "correct": "Total shock fills your body",
    "song": "Revenge - Captain Sparklez"
  },
  {
    "question": "My pick just broke into some shards, scary noise what should i do?",
    "correct": "Go left or right i'll have to chose",
    "song": "Don't mine at night - BebopVox YOGSCAST"
  },
  {
    "question": "You've been hit by, you've been struck by...",
    "correct": "A smooth criminal",
    "song": "Smooth criminal - Michael Jackson"
  },
  {
    "question": "Never gonna make you cry, never gonna say goodbye",
    "correct": "Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you",
    "song": "Never gonna give you up - Rick Astley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fortnite, fortnite let's go",
    "correct": "i get it all night all night for show",
    "song": "Fortnite rap battle - NerdOut"
  },
  {
    "question": "Apple bottom jeans, boots with the fur",
    "correct": "got the whole club looking at her",
    "song": "Low - Flo Rida"
  },
  {
    "question": "Well, the years start coming and they don't stop coming",
    "correct": "Fed to the rules and I hit the ground running",
    "song": "All star - Smash Mouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "It's been so long, since the last time i've seen my son lost to this monster",
    "correct": "To the man behind the slaughter",
    "song": "It's been so long - The living tombstone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since you've been gone, i've been singing this stupid song so i could ponder",
    "correct": "The sanity of your mother",
    "song": "It's been so long - The living tombstone"
  },
  {
    "question": "I believe i can fly",
    "correct": "I believe i can touch the sky",
    "song": "I believe i can fly - R.Kelly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Birds flying high",
    "correct": "You know how i feel",
    "song": "Feeling good - Michael Bublé"
  },
  {
    "question": "Butterflies all having fun",
    "correct": "You know what i mean",
    "song": "Feeling good - Michael Bublé"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bet you don't have this blue",
    "correct": "Bet you don't have this green",
    "song": "Mine all day - PewDiePie"
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't wanna live forever i just wanna",
    "correct": "Die a king",
    "song": "Die a king - IamJakeHill"
  },
  {
    "question": "Drift drift away you're a memory",
    "correct": "I'll only exist if you remember me",
    "song": "Alone Together - Quadeca"
  },
  {
    "question": "Decide man what's the reason they would lie?",
    "correct": "Quadeca on their playlist more than KSI",
    "song": "Insecure - Quadeca"
  }
]